Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Film and Video by Sport, 1937-2006 (Boxes 101-154), 198865
  - Football 2005-2006 and undated, 199688 (Box 126)
    - 10.08.05 Rice Football vs. East Carolina Endzone Tape 1, 199719
    - 10.22.05 Rice Football vs. Navy Highlight Tape 3, 199718
    - 10.08.05 Rice Football vs. East Carolina Highlight Tape 2, 199717
    - 10.15.05 Rice Football vs. Tulsa Highlight Tape 2, 199716
    - 11.2.05 Rice Football vs. Tulane Highlight Tape 1, 199715
    - 10.29.05 Rice Football vs. UTEP Highlight Tape 1, 199714
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Highlight Tape 1, 199713
    - Ready to Soar VHS, 199712
    - The Quest for #1 VHS, 199711
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Sideline Tape 1, 199710
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Sideline Tape 2, 199709
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Sideline Tape 3, 199708
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Sideline Tape 4, 199707
    - 10.01.05 Rice Football vs. UAB Endzone Tape 3, 199706
    - Rice FB/CS UTEP, 199705
    - All-Time Team Bits Super VHS and 2 DVDs, 199704
    - Rice vs. Michigan Continuous Sideline VHS, 199703
    - Rice vs. Michigan Continuous Endzone VHS, 199702
    - Rice vs. Texas Endzone Tape 1, 199701
    - Rice vs. Texas Endzone Tape 2, 199700
    - Rice vs. Texas Endzone Tape 3, 199699
    - Rice vs. Tulane Continuous Endzone VHS, 199698
    - Rice vs. Tulane Continuous Sideline VHS, 199697
    - Team Highlights Tape Rice vs. Texas VHS, 199696
    - Rice vs. Texas Continuous Sideline, 199695
    - Rice vs. Texas Endzone Tape 3, 199694
    - Houston vs. Rice Endzone Tape 1 Beta, 199693
    - Houston vs. Rice Endzone Tape 2 Beta, 199692
    - 2005 Hall of fame CD, 199691
    - 4.18.06 Bobby May retirement CD, 199690
    - 2006 BW Mugs, 199689
  - Baseball 1995-2002, 199649 (Box 127-129)
    - 2.8.00 Reckling Park, 199687
    - 5.31.02 NCAA Regionals Game #1 Rice vs. Harvard, 199686
    - 6.1.02 NCAA Regionals Game #2 Rice vs. Texas Tech, 199685
    - 1998 Rice Baseball H-lights, 199684
    - 2.8.00 Reckling Park Dedications 1st pitch, 199683
    - 5.20.99 Rice Baseball vs. UNLV at Wac Tourney, 199682
    - 5.22.99 Rice Baseball vs. TCU at Wac Championship, 199681
    - 5.21.99 Rice Baseball vs. SJC at Wac Tourney, 199680
    - 2000 Rice Baseball NCAA Regionals, 199679
    - 3.24.01 Baseball vs. Fresno St, 199678
    - 6.11.99 CWS Rice vs. Miami 2, 199677
    - 1997 College World Series Game 2 Rice vs. LU ESPN, 199676
    - 2002 ESPN All Access Game 8: "The Big Play", 199675
    - 1999 Rice Baseball vs. Texas A and M 1999 Tape 1, 199674
    - 1999 Rice Baseball vs. Texas A and M 1999 Tape 2, 199673
    - 3.27.99 Rice Baseball vs. UNLV Highlights, 199672
    - 2.10.01 Rice Baseball vs. GA Tech, 199671
    - 2002 Monte w/Baseball Players, 199670
    - 1997 NCAA College World Series Highlight Video, 199669
    - 95 Jose Cruz Jr. – Rice NCAA South Regional, 199668
    - 1995 Golden Spikes Award USA Baseball (1/2 hr program), 199667
    - 1995 Texas at Rice Game 1, 199666
    - 6.11.99 CWS – Rice vs. Miami Tape 2, 199665
    - 1995 Golden Spikes Award Finalists Highlight Video, 199664
    - 2002 ESPN All Access Game 8: "The Big Play", 199663
    - 5.25.97 NCAA Baseball Tournament Rice vs. SMSU, 199662
    - 6.17.02 College World Series Game 7 Notre Dame vs. Rice University, 199661
    - 1995 TX at Rice Game 1, 199660
    - 6.4.99 USL vs. Rice Game 1, 199659
    - 6.5.99 USL vs. Rice Game 2, 199658
    - 1999 A Golden Year in Omaha 2002 Baseball Post season art, 199657
    - 2002 Baseball art I, 199656
    - 2002 Baseball art, 199655
    - 7.15.04 Clemens Award, 199654
    - 2002 Baseball media Guide, 199653
    - 2002 Baseball Art II, 199652
    - 2002 Baseball Pictures, 199651
    - 2001 Rice Baseball muss and action, 199650
  - Baseball 2003, 199622 (Box 128)
    - 6.18.03 Rice vs. Texas College World Series Game #3; Rice 5 | Texas 4, 199648
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_005 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_006 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.22.03 College World Series Rice vs. Stanford Game #2, 199647
    - 6.23.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship Series, 199646
    - Game #3 Final game, 199645
    - 5.30.03 Rice Baseball vs. McNeese Regional, 199644
    - 5.31.03 Rice Baseball vs. WSU Regional Game #2, 199643
    - 3.28.03 Baseball vs. SJS, 199642
    - 4.1.03 Baseball vs. UH, 199641
    - 6.16.03 Rice vs. Texas, 199640
    - 6.18.03 College World Series Game #2, 199639
    - 6.18.03 College World Series Game #3, 199638
    - 6.21.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship series Game #1 (2 copies), 199637
    - 6.23.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship series Game #3, 199636
    - 6.7.03 Rice vs. UH Superregional ESPN Feed (2 copies), 199635
    - 6.21.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship series Game #1, 199634
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_007 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_008 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.22.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship series Game #2, 199633
    - 6.16.03 Rice vs. Texas College World Series Game #2, 199632
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_003 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_004 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.14.03 Rice vs. SWMS College World Series Game #1, 199631
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_001 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_002 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.22.03 College World Series Championship Series Game 2 Rice vs. Stanford, 199630
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_009 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_010 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.18.03 College World Series Game 12 Texas vs. Rice, 199629
    - 6.23.03 College World Series Championship Series Game #3 Rice vs. Stanford, 199628
      These digital objects are digitized versions of the VHS. UA0155aip_011 is a master file avi. UA0155aip_012 is an access copy mp4.
    - 6.23.03 College World Series Championship Series Game 3 Stanford vs. Rice, 199627
    - 2003 Rice Owls Baseball media Coverage, 199626
    - 6.16.03 College World Series Game 8 Rice vs. Texas, 199625
    - 6.21.03 College World Series Championship Series Game 1 Stanford vs. Rice, 199624
    - 6.14.04 College World Series Game 3 SW Missouri State vs. Rice, 199623
  - Baseball 2003-2004, 199600 (Box 129)
    - 6.1.03 Rice vs. Wichita St. Regional #3 (2 copies), 199621
    - 2003 Rice Baseball Promo World Series Champs, 199620
    - 5.30.04 Rice Baseball vs. McNeese regional, 199619
    - 5.31.03 Rice baseball vs. WSU Regional Game #2, 199618
    - 3.5.04 Baseball vs. Tx St, 199617
    - 3.7.04 Baseball vs. Tx St (2 s), 199616
    - 6.24.03 Rice Baseball Championship KTRK (Ch. 13), 199615
    - 7.14-7.15.04 Roger Clemens Award Dinner and Activities, 199614
    - 2003 Rice Regional highlights, 199613
    - 2003 Rice Baseball Commercials, 199612
    - 6.8.03 Rice vs. UH Superregional Game #2 (3 copies), 199611
    - 6.9.03 Rice vs. UH Superregional Game #3, 199610
    - 6.9.03 Rice vs. UH Superregional Game #3 ESPN, 199609
    - 6.7.03 Rice vs. UH Superregional Game #3, 199608
    - "Rice Owls Win 2003 College World Series" (3 copies), 199607
    - 6.16.03 Rice vs. Texas College World Series Game #2 (2 copies), 199606
    - 6.22.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship Series Game #2, 199605
    - 6.18.93 Rice vs. Texas College World Series Game #3, 199604
    - 6.22.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship Series Game #2 (2 copies), 199603
    - 6.23.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Sports center before game, 199602
    - 6.21.03 Rice vs. Stanford College World Series Championship Series Game #1, 199601
  - Baseball and Men's Basketball, undated, 199584 (Box 130)
    - CWS vs. Alabama Tape 1 beta, 199599
    - CWS vs. Alabama Tape 2 beta (2 copies), 199598
    - CWS vs. Oklahoma St Tape 1 beta, 199597
    - CWS vs. Oklahoma St Tape 2 beta, 199596
    - KHOU – TV Ch. 11 Rice Baseball Highlights beta, 199595
    - Baseball vs. Houston ESPN VHS, 199594
    - CWS vs. Oklahoma St Tape 2 VHS, 199593
    - Rice baseball NCAA regional game 1 tape 3, 199592
    - Rice baseball regionals, 199591
    - Baseball highlight tape – finished product, 199590
    - Parade Rice beta, 199589
    - CWS Rice vs. Miami Tape 4, 199588
    - CWS vs. Oklahoma St Tape 3, 199587
    - Baseball 3/21 beta (2 copies), 199586
    - Baseball masks; Last name Arnold-Tribe (CD), 199585
  - Men's Basketball 1985-1989, 199534 (Box 131)
    Formats: VHS
    - 12.2.88 Marquette vs. Rice, 199583
    - 12.28.88 Rice vs. Northern Ill, 199582
    - 11.25.88 Rice vs. Detroit, 199581
    - 12.3.88 Rice vs. Maine, 199580
    - 1.6.88 Rice vs. Texas Tech, 199579
    - 11.28.88 Rice Owls at Mississippi State, 199578
    - 12.7.88 Rice vs. SMU, 199577
    - 2.7.88 Texas Tech at Rice TV Version, 199576
    - 2.17.88 Rice at SMU, 199575
    - 2.25.89 Rice Owls at Baylor, 199574
    - 12.21.89 Rice Owls vs. Prairie View A and M, 199573
    - 11.17.89 Rice Owls vs. Spirit Express, 199572
    - 2.25.89 Rice Owls at Baylor, 199571
    - 3.1.89 Rice Owls vs. Arkansas, 199570
    - 2.1.89 Rice Owls vs. Eastern New Mexico, 199569
    - 11.27.89 Rice Owls vs. Tulane, 199568
    - 2.11.89 Rice Owls at Texas, 199567
    - 12.30.89 Rice Owls vs. New Hampshire, 199566
    - 2.22.89 Rice Owls at Texas A and M, 199565
    - 2.15.89 Rice Owls vs. TCU, 199564
    - 2.18.89 Rice Owls vs. SMU, 199563
    - 11.9.89 Rice Owls Blue-Gray Game, 199562
    - 2.5.89 Rice Owls vs. Houston, 199561
    - 1.25.89 Rice Owls vs. Baylor, 199560
    - 11.27.85 Rice vs. Montana, 199559
    - 1996 Fresno, 199558
    - 12.5.86 UTSA at Rice, 199557
    - 12.2.87 Rice Owls vs. Mississippi State, 199556
    - 12.5.87 Rice vs. US International University, 199555
    - 10.23.97 Rice Owls Alumni Game, 199554
    - 12.8.87 Rice vs. Southern, 199553
    - 12.29.87 Montana vs. Rice, 199552
    - 11.30.87 Rice vs. UMKC, 199551
    - 12.15.88 Detroit vs. Rice, 199550
    - 1.23.88 Rice Owls at Baylor, 199549
    - 11.11.88 Rice Owls vs. Spirit Express, 199548
    - 1.27.88 Rice Owls vs. Arkansas, 199547
    - 1.16.88 Rice Owls vs. SMU, 199546
    - 1.2.88 Rice Owls vs. Wisconsin-Oshkosh, 199545
    - 1.20.88 Rice Owls at Texas A and M, 199544
    - 1.13.88 Rice Owls vs. TCU, 199543
    - 11.16.88 Rice Owls vs. Australia, 199542
    - 12.28.88 Rice at NIU, 199541
    - 2.3.88 Rice Owls at University of Houston, 199540
    - 12.10.88 Rice Owls vs. Nevada-Reno, 199539
    - 1.10.88 Rice Owls at Texas, 199538
    - 2.24.88 Rice Owls vs. Baylor, 199537
    - 11.3.88 Rice Owls Blue Gray Game, 199536
    - 1.30.88 Rice vs. Lamar, 199535
  - Men's Basketball 1989-1992, 199485 (Box 132)
    - 1.27.90 Rice Owls at Texas, 199533
    - 2.3.90 Rice Owls vs. Missouri-KC, 199532
    - 1.3.90 Rice Owls vs. Detroit, 199531
    - 2.28.90 Rice Owls vs. Texas, 199530
    - 1.6.90 Rice Owls vs. Houston, 199529
    - 2.7.90 Rice Owls at Houston, 199528
    - 2.25.90 Rice Owls vs. Texas Aggies, 199527
    - 1.24.90 Rice Owls at Texas Aggies, 199526
    - 3.9.90 Houston vs. Rice, 199525
    - 12.17.90 Rice at TCU, 199524
    - 1.10.90 Rice at Texas Tech, 199523
    - 2.22.90 Rice at SMU, 199522
    - 1.20.90 Rice at SMU, 199521
    - 1992 SWC Tournament Quarterfinals Rice 62 | Texas Tech 65, 199520
    - 12.9.89 Rice vs. Georgetown, 199519
    - 12.30.92 Rice 70 | at Colorado State 75, 199518
    - 11.23.92 Rice 94 | Arkansas Express 66, 199517
    - 12.05.92 Rice at Washington, 199516
    - 12.20.92 Rice 60 | Xavier 75, 199515
    - 12.19.92 Rice 65 | Delaware 71 NCAA Ball-Japan, 199514
    - 1.18.92 Rice vs. Houston, 199513
    - 12.18.92 Rice 94 | Japanese All-stars 56, 199512
    - 1991-92 Rice Highlight Tape, 199511
    - 9.10.92 Rice Basketball Highlights, 199510
    - 11.13.89 Rice Owls vs. Brazil, 199509
    - 11.17.89 Rice Owls vs. Spirit Express, 199508
    - 1.20.90 Rice Owls vs. SMU, 199507
    - 2.10.90 Rice Owls vs. Texas Tech, 199506
    - 1.17.90 Rice Owls vs. TCU, 199505
    - 1.6.90 Rice Owls vs. Houston, 199504
    - 2.28.90 Rice Owls vs. Texas, 199503
    - 1.7.89 Rice Owls vs. Texas Tech, 199502
    - 2.1.89 Rice Owls vs. Eastern New Mexico, 199501
    - 12.4.89 Rice Owls vs. Wisconsin- Plattevile, 199500
    - 1.11.89 Rice Owls vs. Texas, 199499
    - 1.21.89 Rice Owls vs. Texas A and M, 199498
    - 2.11.89 Rice Owls at Texas, 199497
    - 1.7.89 Texas Tech at Rice TV Version, 199496
    - 3.10.89 SWC Tournament Game 3 Arkansas-Rice, 199495
    - 1.15.89 Rice vs. TCU, 199494
    - 1.28.89 Arkansas vs. Rice, 199493
    - 12.9.89 Rice vs. Georgetown, 199492
    - 11.24.887 Rice vs. Colorado, 199491
    - 11.28.89 Rice vs. Marquette TV Version, 199490
    - 12.2.89 Rice vs. Duquesne, 199489
    - 11.30.89 Rice vs. Indiana St, 199488
    - 3.3.90 Rice at Arkansas, 199487
    - 3.9.90 Houston vs. Rice SWC Tournament, 199486
  - Men's Basketball 1992-1994, 199437 (Box 133)
    Formats: Beta, VHS
    - 3.6.93 Rice 76 | Texas A and M 82, 199484
    - 1.12.93 Rice 66 | Texas A and M 65, 199483
    - 1.9.93 Rice 89 | Mississippi 79, 199482
    - 11.13.93 Blue-Gray Game, 199481
    - 1.7.93 Rice 83 | Fairfield 72, 199480
    - 1.9.93 Rice 89 | at Mississippi 79, 199479
    - 1.27.93 Ole Miss 67 | at Rice 72, 199478
    - 2.2.93 Rice 65 | at Houston 61, 199477
    - 1.16.93 Rice 84 | TCU 65, 199476
    - 2.24.93 Rice 67 | at Fordham 69, 199475
    - 1.7.93 Rice 83 | Fairfield 72, 199474
    - 1.30.93 Rice 101 | Texas 83, 199473
    - 1.20.93 Rice 67 | Texas Tech 59, 199472
    - 1.23.93 Rice 87 | Baylor 96, 199471
    - 2.2.93 Rice 65 | at Houston 61, 199470
    - 2.24.93 Rice 67 | at Fordham 69, 199469
    - 1.5.93 Rice 92 | Texas 87, 199468
    - 2.5.94 Rice vs. U of H, 199467
    - 1.11.94 Rice vs. SMU, 199466
    - 1.19.94 Rice at TCU, 199465
    - 3.10.94 Baylor vs. Rice, 199464
    - 1994 Rice vs. Virginia, 199463
    - 11.26.94 Rice vs. Nevada, 199462
    - 12.30.94 Kent vs. Rice, 199461
    - 2.17.93 Rice 84 | Baylor 77, 199460
    - 2.20.93 Rice vs. Texas Tech, 199459
    - 2.13.93 Rice 68 | at TCU 50, 199458
    - 1.12.93 Rice 66 | at Texas A and M 65, 199457
    - 3.3.93 Rice vs. U Houston, 199456
    - 11.18.93 Rice vs. Minn at Minn Preseason NIT 1st round ESPN, 199455
    - 12.30.93 Rice vs. New Mexico, 199454
    - 12.1.93 Rice vs. Sam Houston, 199453
    - 1993-94 Rice Basketball Jamfest, 199452
    - 1993 Rice Basketball Recap, 199451
    - 1.30.93 Rice 101 | Texas 83, 199450
    - 9.10.92 Rice Basketball Highlights, 199449
    - 1.5.93 Rice at Texas, 199448
    - 2.27.93 Rice 90 | SMU 67, 199447
    - 3.6.93 Rice 76 | Texas A and M 82, 199446
    - 2.24.93 Rice 67 | at Fordham 69, 199445
    - 1.23.93 Rice 87 | at Baylor 96, 199444
    - 3.4.93 Rice vs. SMU, 199443
    - 2.6.93 Rice 77 | at SMU 78, 199442
    - 2.13.93 Rice 68 | at TCU 50, 199441
    - 1.9.93 Rice 89 | at Mississippi 79, 199440
    - 2.6.93 Rice 77 | at SMU 78, 199439
    - 1.30.93 Rice 101 | Texas 83, 199438
  - Men's Basketball 1994-1995, 199389 (Box 134)
    - 1994-95 MBB Media Guides/1995 MBB art (3MDC), 199436
    - 2.4.95 Rice vs. Texas, 199435
    - 11.28.95 Rice vs. North Texas, 199434
    - 12.2.95 Rice vs. Kent State, 199433
    - 11.17.95 Rice vs. Conoco, 199432
    - 11.24.95 Rice at Yale, 199431
    - 12.2.95 Rice at Kent State, 199430
    - 12.30.95 Rice vs. Central Michigan, 199429
    - 2.19.95 Rice at TCU, 199428
    - 2.1.95 Texas Tech vs. Rice, 199427
    - 2.26.95 Rice at Texas Tech, 199426
    - 1.11.95 Rice at Houston, 199425
    - 11.28.94 Sam Houston vs. Rice, 199424
    - 12.10.94 Virginia at Rice, 199423
    - 11.17.94 Rice vs. Brazil, 199422
    - 11.11.94 Rice vs. Conoco, 199421
    - 12.28.94 Rice vs. Holy Cross, 199420
    - 2.13.94 Rice at SMU, 199419
    - 2.16.94 Rice vs. TCU (2 copies), 199418
    - 1.11.94 Rice Hoops #2 Airdate, 199417
    - 2.8.94 Rice Hoops #6 Airdate, 199416
    - 2.15.94 Rice Hoops #7 Airdate, 199415
    - 12.9.95 Rice at Vanderbilt, 199414
    - 3.19.95 Rice vs. TCU ESPN 2, 199413
    - 1.5.95 Rice vs. Montana, 199412
    - 1.7.95 Rice vs. Boise State, 199411
    - 3.10.94 SWC Tourney 1st round games, 199410
    - 1.22.94 Rice at OKU, 199409
    - 1.11.94 Rice vs. SMU, 199408
    - 3.11.94 Texas vs. Rice, 199407
    - 2.20.94 Rice vs. OALM, 199406
    - 2.1.94 Rice at Texas, 199405
    - 11.28.94 Centenary vs. Rice, 199404
    - 1.8.94 Rice vs. Montana, 199403
    - 12.22.94 Rice vs. Kansas, 199402
    - 12.28.94 Rice vs. Holy Cross, 199401
    - 12.22.94 Rice at Kansas, 199400
    - 3.2.94 Rice vs. Texas, 199399
    - 1.16.94 Rice vs. A and M, 199398
    - 1.3.94 Rice vs. Boise St, 199397
    - 2.26.94 Rice vs. Tech, 199396
    - 1.26.94 Rice vs. Baylor, 199395
    - 3.5.94 Rice at U of H, 199394
    - 1.4.94 Rice Hoops #1 Airdate, 199393
    - 1.18.94 Rice Hoops #3 Airdate, 199392
    - 1.25.94 Rice Hoops #4 Airdate, 199391
    - 1994-1995 Rice University Basketball Year in Review (VHS W/2 DVDS), 199390
  - Men's Basketball 1995-1996, 199340 (Box 135)
    - 2.21.96 Rice vs. TCU (2 copies), 199388
    - 3.2.96 Rice at Texas Tech, 199387
    - 11.26.96 Rice vs. Colorado Sch. of Mines, 199386
    - 11.17.96 Rice vs. Athletes in Action, 199385
    - 11.22.96 Rice vs. HBU, 199384
    - 12.30.96 Rice vs. Navy, 199383
    - 12.20.96 Rice vs. Southern, 199382
    - 12.22.96 Rice vs. North Texas, 199381
    - 12.6.96 Rice vs. Princeton, 199380
    - 11.17.96 Rice vs. AIA Defense, 199379
    - 12.7.96 Rice vs. Prairie View, 199378
    - 11.29.96 Rice at Florida State, 199377
    - 2.7.96 Rice vs. Texas, 199376
    - 1.29.96 Rice vs. Southern, 199375
    - 1996 Rice Bball Csc Open and Close, 199374
    - 1.30.96 TCU 2nd half, 199373
    - 9.9.96 Rice Owls Men's Basketball, 199372
    - 12.22.96 Rice at North Texas, 199371
    - 11.26.96 Rice at Colorado School of Mines CBK: Rice/Florida State, 199370
    - 12.3.96 Rice vs. St. Bonnie, 199369
    - 12.7.96 Rice vs. Prairie View A and M, 199368
    - 12.30.96 Rice vs. Navy, 199367
    - 12.2.96 Rice at St. Bonaventure, 199366
    - 1.13.96 Rice vs. Houston, 199365
    - 2.11.96 SMU at Rice, 199364
    - 1.22.95 Rice vs. TCU ESPN 2, 199363
    - 12.2.95 Kent State Hi-lites, 199362
    - 1.17.95 Rice vs. A and M, 199361
    - 1.14.95 Rice at SMU, 199360
    - 2.11.95 SMU at Rice, 199359
    - 1.28.95 Rice at Baylor, 199358
    - 1.25.95 Rice vs. Southern, 199357
    - 2.11.95 SMU at Rice, 199356
    - 2.8.95 Houston vs. Rice, 199355
    - 3.9.95 Rice vs. Texas, 199354
    - 2.19.95 Rice at TCU, 199353
    - 2.22.95 Oral Roberts vs. Rice, 199352
    - 11.29.96 Rice at Florida State, 199351
    - 1.17.95 Rice Hoops Show, 199350
    - 2.7.95 Rice Hoops Show, 199349
    - 2.14.95 Rice Hoops Show, 199348
    - 3.4.95 Texas at Rice (2 copies), 199347
    - 3.10.95 Rice vs. Texas, 199346
    - 3.1.95 Baylor at Rice, 199345
    - 2.15.95 Rice at Texas A and M, 199344
    - 2.26.95 Rice at Texas Tech, 199343
    - 1.02.95 Rice vs. TCU, 199342
    - 3.7.95 Rice Hoops Show, 199341
  - Men's Basketball 1996-1997, 199290 (Box 136)
    Formats: VHS, beta
    - 1.16.97 Rice vs. UTEP, 199339
    - 3.1.97 Rice at TCU, 199338
    - 2.1.97 Rice vs. SMU, 199337
    - 1.6.97 Rice vs. Fresno State, 199336
    - 2.6.97 Rice vs. Tulsa, 199335
    - 2.27.97 Rice at SMU, 199334
    - Rice v. AFA Hi-light #2, 199333
    - 12.5.97 ESPN Plus Rice vs. Iowa Chevy Shootout, 199332
    - Rice v. AFA Hi-lite #3, 199331
    - 1996-97 Rice Owls Basketball Highlight Film, 199330
    - 1996 Highs Men's Basketball, 199329
    - Rice vs. AFA Highlight #1, 199328
    - 11.10.94 Rice vs. Slovakia, 199327
    - 1997 Rice vs. Missouri-Rolla, 199326
    - 11.17.97 Kansas vs. Rice, 199325
    - 12.21.97 Rice vs. Centenary, 199324
    - 1997 Rice vs. Stetson, 199323
    - 11.10.97 Rice vs. Slovakia, 199322
    - 1997 FSU at Rice, 199321
    - 11.10.97 Rice vs. Slovakia, 199320
    - 12.06.97 Rice vs. Mount St. Mary's, 199319
    - 11.30.97 Rice vs. USF San Juan Shootout, 199318
    - 11.29.07 West Virginia vs. Rice San Juan Shootout, 199317
    - 9.9.97 Rice Owl's Men's Basketball, 199316
    - 1.13.97 Rice vs. Tulsa ESPN Copy, 199315
    - 12.5.97 Rice at Iowa, 199314
    - 2.26.96 TCU at A and M, 199313
    - 1996 Rice at SMU, 199312
    - 1.17.96 Rice vs. SMU, 199311
    - 3.3.96 Rice at Texas Tech, 199310
    - 3.3.96 BYU vs. Utah, 199309
    - 1.22.96 Rice at TCU, 199308
    - 2.3.96 Rice vs. Texas Tech, 199307
    - 3.8.96 Texas Tech vs. Rice, 199306
    - 1.6.96 Rice 80 | Texas 69, 199305
    - 1.9.96 Rice vs. Baylor, 199304
    - 3.7.96 TCU vs. Rice, 199303
    - 2.8.97 Rice vs. Fresno St, 199302
    - 1.23.97 Rice at BYU, 199301
    - 1.30.97 Rice vs. TCU, 199300
    - 1.6.97 Rice vs. Fresno St, 199299
    - 2.8.97 Fresno State vs. Rice, 199298
    - 2.13.97 Rice at New Mexico, 199297
    - 11.28.97 Evansville vs. Rice San Juan Shootout, 199296
    - 1.18.97 Rice vs. New Mexico, 199295
    - 11.13.97 Rice at Tulsa, 199294
    - 1996-97 Rice Owls Basketball Highlight Film, 199293
    - 1996-97 Basketball highlights, 199292
    - 3.1.97 Rice at TCU, 199291
  - Men's Basketball 1998-1999, 199246 (Box 137)
    - 1998-99 Rice vs. Southern (2 copies SVHS), 199289
    - 2.20.99 Tulsa vs. Rice, 199288
    - 1.23.99 Rice vs. Tulsa, 199287
    - 2.4.99 CSU vs. Rice, 199286
    - 2.6.99 Rice at Wyoming, 199285
    - 1.7.99 Wyoming vs. Rice, 199284
    - 1.2.99 Portland vs. Rice, 199283
    - 1.9.99 Colorado St vs. Rice, 199282
    - 1.30.99 Rice vs. TCU, 199281
    - 1.14.99 Rice at UNLV, 199280
    - 2.13.99 Rice vs. UNLV, 199279
    - 1999 Rice Hilites, 199278
    - 1999 Rice vs. Tulsa beta, 199277
    - 1999 Rice vs. Missouri-Rolla Tape 1, 199276
    - 1999 Rice vs. Louisiana College Tape 2, 199275
    - 2.25.99 Rice at TCU Tape 1, 199274
    - 11.15.99 Rice vs. Athlete's 1st Tape 1, 199273
    - 1999 Rice at WAC Tourn vs. New Mexico Tape 1, 199272
    - 1998 Rice CBK/CS (Wilson) (5 copies beta), 199271
    - 1998-99 Rice vs. Houston Flight Tape 2 (beta), 199270
    - 2.25.97 Rice at TCU, 199269
    - 12.22.98 Rice vs. St. Mary's, 199268
    - 12.5.98 Rice vs. Holy Cross, 199267
    - 12.9.98 Rice vs. Louisiana College, 199266
    - 12.20.98 Rice vs. Southern, 199265
    - 11.23.98 Rice vs. Missouri-Rolla, 199264
    - 1.31.98 SMU vs. Rice, 199263
    - 12.1.98 Rice vs. SFA, 199262
    - 12.4.98 Weber State vs. Rice, 199261
    - 11.13.98 Rice vs. Pan American, 199260
    - 1.21.98 Rice vs. Houston, 199259
    - 2.14.98 STSU vs. Rice, 199258
    - 1.6.98 Houston Flight vs. Rice, 199257
    - 2.21.98 SDSU vs. Rice Fox Sports Copy, 199256
    - 1.31.98 Rice at SMU, 199255
    - 1.13.98 Rice vs. SJSU, 199254
    - 2.19.98 SJSU vs. Rice, 199253
    - 1.11.98 Rice vs. Tulsa TV, 199252
    - 1.13.98 Rice vs. San Jose, 199251
    - 1.17.98 Fresno State vs. Rice, 199250
    - 2.21.98 SDSU at Rice, 199249
    - 1.24.98 SDSU vs. Rice, 199248
    - 1.24.98 Rice vs. SDSU TV, 199247
  - Men's Basketball 1999, 199204 (Box 138)
    Formats: Beta
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. University of Houston Tape 2 beta, 199245
    - 11.22.99 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Loyola Tape 2, 199244
    - 1.16.99 Rice Men's Basketball at Loyola Tape 2, 199243
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at WAC Tourn vs. SJS Tape 2, 199242
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at SMU/TCU Tape 3, 199241
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Houston Flight Tape 2, 199240
    - 1.16.99 Rice Men's Basketball at Air Force Tape 3, 199239
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. International team Tape 1, 199238
    - 12.11.99 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Texas A and MTape 2, 199237
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. TCU Tape 2, 199236